trainstationgame.com 2014-12-31

# PIXELFEDERATION EULA

## Privacy policy

**By accessing any of the games created by PIXEL FEDERATION, s.r.o. (“PIXEL”) an End-User agrees to the terms of the most recent version of this Privacy Policy. By agreeing, the End-User authorizes PIXEL to collect and use End-User´s personal information as outlined below. In the event the End-User does not agree with this Privacy Policy, the only recourse of the End-User is to cease use of the PIXEL´s online games - TrainStation, Diggy´s Adventure, Emporea: The Realms of War & Magic ("GAMES") offered on this PixelPortal Site http://portal.pixelfederation.com ("PORTAL").**

**WHAT IS PERSONAL INFORMATION AND WHEN DOES PIXEL COLLECT IT?**. 

As "Personal Information" can be cosidered different kind of information. PIXEL define "Personal Information" as information that identifies the End-User and that can be used to contact the End-User (online or offline). PIXEL may collect personal information from our online visitors during: 

  * PORTAL registration and prize acceptance;
  * Warranty registration and requests;
  * Customer support and/or technical service requests;
  * Player match up and other head-to-head online competitions;
  * Registration for games and/or special game-specific events;
  * Newsletter subscriptions, referral services, and other marketing surveys and email campaigns
  * Registration for service accounts;
  * Creation of a personal profile;
  * Product, service and/or subscription orders;
  * Service requests from third party service providers on our PORTAL;
  * Access to PIXEL GAMES (products) and/or services on social networks or other third party services
  * Otherwise through use of our software, mobile or online services where personal information is required for use and/or participation.

Personal Information can include things like name, date of birth, e-mail address, gender, Facebook friends, etc. of the End-User. 

**WHAT NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES PIXEL COLLECT?**

In addition to Personal Information, PIXEL collects a variety of data that could not be used to identify or contact the End-User. Data are used to enhance the quality of the GAMES and other services. Here are some of the forms of non-personal information PIXEL collects: 

**Game Play Information:** PIXEL may collect and retain information relating to the End-User´s interaction with the GAMES. For example, PIXEL may monitor the length of time the the End-User plays a game, the number and type of activities the End-User participates in during a particular session, and the End-User´s scores. 

**General Use Information:** PIXEL may also collect general information about the End-User´s interaction with PIXEL product such as the End-User´s internet protocol address, browser type, referring and exit URLs, click amounts, domain names, pages viewed, the amount of time spent viewing a particular page, the time of such activities, etc. 

**GENERATED CONTENT BY THE END-USER**

It is possible the End-User may choose to share additional information about himself through the End-User´s generated content. A generated content by the End-User may be defined as various kinds of content, publicly available, that are produced by the End-User (for example, wall posts, messages, and actions with other end users). 

It is possible that the generated content the End-User choose to provide may contain Personal Information. The End-User is aware that PIXEL cannot guarantee protection for information the End-User makes available publicly through things such as comments, wall posts, etc. Additionally, it is likely that the generated content by the End-User will be disseminated broadly through third parties such as Facebook. Further, the End-User should be aware that such public data may be harvested by third parties with access to it (such as other users) and PIXEL cannot control those third parties' use of such information. 

**WHAT PIXEL DOES NOT DO WITH THE END-USER INFORMATION**

PIXEL Does Not Sell, Lease, Rent Or Transfer the End-User´s Personal Information. PIXEL collects information for the purpose of improving the services. PIXEL may make certain aggregate information available to third parties (as outlined below), but PIXEL will not sell, rent, lease or otherwise transfer the End-User´s Personal Information to any third parties except as provided below. 

PIXEL May Log, But PIXEL Will Not Disclose, Individual Internet Protocol Addresses: PIXEL may maintain log files which contain IP addresses for purposes such as traffic monitoring. As the End-User knows, an IP address is a numeric address assigned to the End-User´s computer (or router) by the End-User´s Internet Service Provider. PIXEL will not disclose individual IP addresses to third parties. 

The End-User is aware, PIXEL will disclose information, including Personal Information, to the extent it may be necessary to prevent harm to third parties or it is required by law (as we specify below). 

**WHAT PIXEL MAY DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION**

Thereinafter are some of the things PIXEL may do with the information collected by PIXEL. This includes both Personal Information and non-personal information. If PIXEL determines there are additional things PIXEL would like to do, this section will be amended. 

**Improvement of PIXEL Services.**

PIXEL may collect and retain information relating to the End-User´s interaction with the GAMES. For example, PIXEL may monitor the length of time the the End-User plays a game, the number and type of activities the End-User participates in during a particular session, and the End-User´s scores. 

**Notifications.**

PIXEL may also collect general information about the End-User´s interaction with PIXEL product such as the End-User´s internet protocol address, browser type, referring and exit URLs, click amounts, domain names, pages viewed, the amount of time spent viewing a particular page, the time of such activities, etc. 

**Aggregate Data.**

Occasionally, Personal Information and non-personal information is more useful when PIXEL lump it in a big pile to get a better understanding of the general characteristics of PIXEL´s End-Users-base. For example, knowing that 30% of PIXEL´s End-Users are playing from a particular location may be important. PIXEL may disclose these general statistics (which will not include information capable of identifying or contacting any particular End-User) to enhance customer service, tailor the GAMES to the End-User interests or optimize the GAMES. 

**Legal Requests and Harm Prevention.**

PIXEL may disclose information pursuant to subpoenas, court orders, or other requests if PIXEL has a good faith belief that the response is required by law. PIXEL may also share information when PIXEL has a good faith belief it is necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activity, to prevent imminent bodily harm, or to protect PIXEL and the End-User from people violating the Terms of Service. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, courts or other government entities. 

**Transfer in the Event of Sale or Change of Control.**

If the ownership of all or substantially all of PIXEL´s business changes, PIXEL may transfer the End-User information to the new owner so that the services PIXEL provides the End-User can continue to operate. In such a case, the End-User´s information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy. 

**SECURITY OF THE PORTAL**

PIXEL uses encryption and authentication tools to protect the security of the information that the End-User shares with PIXEL. Once PIXEL receives the End-User´s transmission, PIXEL will do it´s best to protect its security on PIXEL´s systems. For example, PIXEL protects personal information that was gathered on a secured server behind a firewall; it is not directly connected to the Internet. 

Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed 100% secure. As a result, while PIXEL strives to protect the End-User´s personal information, PIXEL cannot guarantee the security of any information the End-User transmits to or from PORTAL, and the End-User does so at his own risk. Accordingly, PIXEL disclaims liability for any theft, loss, or interception of or any unauthorized access or damage to any data or communications. By using the PORTAL, the End-User acknowledges understanding and agrees to assume these risks. 

**COOKIES**

PIXEL may use cookies. A "cookie" is small file that PIXEL saves on the End-User´s computer's hard drive that contains non-personal information. These cookies help to give the End-User faster access to pages the End-User has already visited. They also allow the End-User to personalize his pages and optimize his experience in the GAMES. PIXEL also uses cookies to help figuring out how many people visit PORTAL and how they interact with the GAMES. The End-User can disable cookies on his computer by indicating this in the preference or options menus in his browser. Disabling cookies may prevent the End-User from properly using the GAMES or accessing the PORTAL. 

**CHILDREN AND PRIVACY**

The GAMES are not directed to children under the age of 18 years. PIXWEL will never request personally identifiable information from anyone whom PIXEL knows to be under the age of 18 without verifiable parental consent. By using the GAMES, the End-User represents and warrants that he is at least 18 years old. If PIXEL becomes aware that the End-User is under the age of 18 and has registered without prior verifiable parental consent, PIXEL will remove that the End-User's personal information. 

**QUESTIONS**

If you need any other information, please submit your requests or questions to info at [privacy@pixelfederation.sk](mailto:privacy@pixelfederation.sk)

**MISCELLANEOUS**

PORTAL may contain links to other websites. PIXEL is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. PIXEL encourages the End-Users to be aware when they leave PORAL to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by PIXEL. 

PIXEL reserves the right to to amend the Privacy Policy of any of the GAMES at any time without prior notice. Amendments will be effective as of the moment of publication on the PORTAL. An End-User is responsible to be acquainted with the latest version of Privacy Policy.
